phonebooky.com 2018-01-31

# Privacy Policy | Booky

_Last modified 15 Aug 2015_

## Introduction

Scrambled Eggs Pte Ltd its subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, the "Company," "we," "our" or "us") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. We will never share your personally identifiable information with third parties without your consent.

This policy describes: 

  * The types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you;
  * Visit, access or use our websites or online applications that run on smart phones, tablets and other devices which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and our websites ("apps");
  * Communicate with us electronically and through other means;
  * View or click on our ads or other online content; and
  * Interact with us through social media websites and other websites and apps.
  * Our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting and disclosing that information.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is to refrain from using our websites or apps. By accessing or using our websites or apps, you agree to this privacy policy.

## Information we collect

Depending on which of our services you use and how you interact with our websites and apps, we collect different kinds of information from or about you, including the below information.

## Account information

 **Contact information** that allows us to communicate with you. We obtain this information when you order or register for our products or services or our apps. This may include information such as your name, telephone number, e-mail address and other identifiers by which you may be contacted online or offline.

 **Payment information** related to your financial relationship with us, such as the services and products we provide to you, your payment information, such as credit and debit card information (we do not store credit and debit card information on our system) and your payment history.

 **Profile information** such as your date of birth, gender, general location (if you authorize Facebook logon).

 **Product/Service usage information** related to the products and services we provide to you, including:

  * Information about your redemption of our offers; and 
  * How you use your devices to access our websites and apps, including the screens you visit and searches you make.

 **Third party partner information** related to how you use our third party partners, such as your reviews of our merchant partners.

 **Your communications with us** by social media, e-mail, electronic messages and other electronic and non-electronic communications.

 **Your Networks and Connections** made available to us, depending on the permissions you have granted, from your mobile and desktop devices.

 **Device and Settings Information** from or about the computers, phones or other devices where you install or access our products or services, depending on the permissions you have granted us. We may collect your device attributes such as:

  * The make and model (mobile phones only);
  * The operating system, hardware version, device settings, file and software names and types, and device identifiers;
  * Device locations, such as through GPS, Bluetooth or WiFi signals; and
  * Connection information such as the name of your mobile operator or ISP, browser type, language and time zone, mobile phone number and IP address.

## How we use the information we collect

We use the information that you provide to us or that we collect about you to:

  *  **Present our websites, apps and their contents to you,** and provide you with information, products or services that you request from us.
  *  **Carry out our obligations** and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  *  **Provide, improve and develop our products and services** to help you get the most value out of the products you purchase, including maximizing the savings you achieve from using the products.
  *  **Communicate with you** about our products and services and respond to you when you contact us.
  *  **Display and measure our advertisements and services** so we can show you relevant advertisements and measure the effectiveness of our advertisements and reach of our products and services.
  *  **Promote security** by using the information collected to verify accounts and activity to promote security on our websites and apps. The usage information we collect helps us to improve our websites and apps and to deliver a better and more personalized experience by enabling us to:
    * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns in order to better manage the demands on our network infrastructure.
    * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our websites and apps according to your individual interests.
    * Speed up your searches.
    * Recognize you when you use our websites and apps.

## How we collect the information

 **You provide information to us when you:**

  * Fill-in forms on our websites and apps, including forms to register to use our websites or apps, make purchases, request further services or post material on our websites.
  * Correspond with us (including e-mail addresses and phone numbers), if you contact us.
  * Respond to surveys we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Perform search queries on our websites or apps.

 **We may automatically collect information** through automatic data collection and tracking technologies when you use our products or services, or interact with our websites or apps, or certain of our partners' websites or apps.

## Third-party information collection

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on our websites and apps are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers and application providers. When you use our websites or apps or their content, certain third parties may use automatic information collection technologies to collect information about you or your device. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our websites or apps. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites, apps and other online services websites. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioural) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly.

## How we share the information we collect

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by the Company about our websites or apps users is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law or legal process, including responding to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our Terms of Service and Rules and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our customers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update our privacy policy from time to time. If we make material changes to our privacy policy, we will post the updated privacy policy on this page.

The effective date of the privacy policy is the "Last Modified" date identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable e-mail address and/or phone number for you and for periodically visiting this privacy policy to check for any changes.

## Contact information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at: [ support@phonebooky.com](mailto:support@phonebooky.com?Subject=Privacy%20Policy "Send as an email")

138 Cecil Street   
#18-00 Cecil Court   
Singapore 069538
